T
About a billion years ago...
During the Cretaceous Period,
The Earth was ruled by Reptiles.
Among them, the one suitably labeled King,
Was this Tyrannosaurus Rex.
Wow. This is...
A fragment of a Dinosaur?
Is this real?
Of course it is.
It was found in the National Park in Utah.
It's a present from my Dad's trip to America.
Well, well...
Let me have a closer look.
Hey, hang on!
So this was living and moving
around a billion years ago?
Hey, let me have a look too.
Here, Shizuka-chan, take a closer look at it.
When I stare at it like this, it's as if
I can see a picture of that period.
With the densely overgrown fern forests,
And Dinosaurs the size of hills.
Come on. Hurry and let me have a look too.
Okay, okay. That's enough.
I'm going to put it away.
I don't want it to get broken.
Geez...
Suneo-kun, thank you for showing
us something so precious.
If you want to see it again, stop by anytime.
Da Hell! Don't brag because of a mere fossil.
Huh??
I will declare this here.
I won't just find a fossil of a claw, but
I will find an entire Dinosaur fossil!
Oops.
I said something I shouldn't have once again.
What?! You making stuff up again?
I'm not lying!
If I am, I'll eat spaghetti through my nose!
Uh-oh, I have a bad habit of spouting
nonsense when I'm vexed.
Now I absolutely have to find a Dinosaur fossil
And a whole one no less.
EH?!
A whole Dinosaur fossil??!
Doraemon, please.
You need to think about where it's possible
or not before you say things.
Doraemon, you're the only
one that can help me...
Pleeease.
Ne?
Listen up, Nobita-kun.
Japan never had any Tyrranosauruses here.
Eh?
How do you propose I produce
a non-existant Dinosaur fossil?
Can't you do something?
I'm telling you...
You're so irresponsible,
Or rather inconsiderate,
Or rather incompetent...
Enough!!
I can't back down now.
H'll do it myself, so don't bother!
I wonder where he gathered all that from...
But with that brain of his, I doubt
that he understands half of it.
I'm sure he'll probably get bored
and quit pretty quickly.
It's commendable that he tries to
work things out on his own,
It doesn't matter if he screws up.
I'll kindly watch over him.
What do you want?
I'm trying to show you my
kindly watching over.
Don't bother me by looking
at me with that dopey grin.
Hmph!
What is this?
Fossils are located in the oldest
Geological Stratum.
Stratum can be seen as layers of dirt
revealed by Earthquakes or mining
Oh, I see...
My instinct tells me this is the ideal spot.
T
I thought I'd find something...
But I guess I was off.
HEY YOU!!
What are you doing up there?
What were you doing up there?
I'm sorry.
I was just about to quit, so don't worry.
It's not about you quitting
Take a look.
Eh? I did all that?
Yeah, you did. What are you
going to do about it?
What should I do?
Let's see...
Then, dig me a hole for my rubbish.
More digging?
Of all the things... have to do this. It's
all because Doraemon refused to help.
Huh?
It's a Dinosaur egg!!
YAAAYYY!!!
I finally found it!
I did it! I did it! I did it!
Hey you! Wait!!
Doraemon!
It's a Dinosaur egg
Look! Look! How about it?
I found this all by myself.
Are you proud of me?
But, how do you know that
this is a Dinosaur egg?
It might be just a rock,
And even if it were a fossil, it could
be a Prehistoric seed or something.
Or it could be a Mammoth Dung.
Dung?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, you don't know what it is, right?
Don't say such things.
Even so, there's no way to
know for sure what it is.
What should do, Doraemon?!
I remember using it before.
Anything wrapped in this will go back in time.
If I make this fossil go back in time
a billion years just like this,
Then we'll find out its true identity for sure.
Yes.
That's the right thing to do.
Lately, it seems you've developed a
habit of relying on me too much.
If it continues, then you'll never
develop independence.
I hope that you will think for yourself, and
solve problems using your own strengths.
I will quietly and gently watch over you, okay?
This is taking a while.
Of course, it DOES have to
go back a billion years...
Huh?
Yay!
There's no mistake, it's an egg!
Yoshin
I'm gonna hatch it!
Oh my.
What are you doing? It's still midday.
If you want to send someone to
the store, have Doraemon go.
I'm busy right now.
No! Let go!
Hey, Nobita!
Come on!
Such a troublesome kid.
Papa, please do something
Nobita's been sleeping while it's still midday.
Nobita!
What's going on?
Oh no...wait
It's that...come over here...
He'll get over it soon, so let's leave him be.
Yoshi.
There's some hope.
Just a bit more. I'm gonna try hard.
Oh, no.
Doraemon!
Wake up!
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey!
I said, hey!
I move around in my sleep,
and the egg is getting cold,
Could you tie me up with this?
Well, aren't you having it hard?
Then...
Goodnight.
Doraemon!
Untie me! Hurry!!
Hurry!
But I just tied you up.
Never mind that!! I'm about to pee my pants!!
It hatched!
There, there.
Doraemon!
Well, do you see?
How about it?
Try saying 'Guu
Well, I'm surprised.
This is a Plesiosaur identified
as 'Futaba-Suzuki-Ryu'
Futaba-Suzuki-Ryu?
Yeah.
It used to live in the waters near Japan
during the Cretaceous Period.
I wonder if he thinks I'm his parent?
There, there. You're such a cutie.
I will call you...
know!
It'll be 'P-suke!
I'll name you P-suke!
Hey, let's call Suneo guys and surprise them.
Wait.
That's where you're fast at jumping the gun.
What?
Think about it.
What good will it do to show them something so small?
I know for sure they'll say it's a lizard and laugh at me.
Besides that...
Don't-don't tell me...
Yes, I'm gonna raise him. Till
he's at least ten meters.
And let's shoot for the biggest
surprise when I reveal him.
I wonder what I should feed him.
No idea.
I guess I'll go get some worms.
Lately, it's been hard to find earth worms.
I'm not finding any.
Hey Nobita. Have you been practicing?
Practicing what?
Practicing eating spaghetti through your nose.
Eh?
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
Dare they mock me like that. Take this and this.
Is the water hot enough?
Yeah, it's just right.
Yes I did.
You heated the water?
P-suke!
What's going on?
Mama, you're such a Dino-killer!!
P-suke!
The Time Furoshiki.
Nobita-kun!
P-suke!
Doraemon!
Hey, hey, hey. Come over here.
P-suke! My P-suke...
I moved him here.
Psuke
Here, P-suke.
He won't eat.
Maybe he doesn't like earth worms.
What's the matter?
Isn't Sashimi your favorite?
Yeah, I want to take my time
eating this in my room.
Me-me too.
Do you like it, Pasuke?
Eat plenty so you can grow big quickly.
Nobita-kun,
Instead of doing something so time consuming,
Why don't you give him this?
What's that?
Growth Acceleration Tablets.
If you give him these, he'll grow better.
Really? Thanks a lot.
I'm home!
P-suke!
Were you lonely?
Now, let's play.
There.
Good. Good
Here it goes.
There
Yoshi. One more.
Here, that's good. Now over there.
Nobita-kun,
Putting him in a cramped closet
day after day is bad for him,
Plus his play area is small too.
Yeah.
Maybe I should take him
for a walk for a change.
Take him outside?!
When everyone sees P-suke, I'm
sure it'll cause a big panic.
Just wait and see.
I'll surprise everyone.
A dinosaur pet,
I bet will be Japan's...no, the
world's most talked about.
Then they'll take P-suke away.
The scientists will either disect him for research,
Or he'll be put in a zoo for viewing.
In either case, it'll be hard for
P-suke to live in this world.
P-suke!
P-suke...
Soon I'll take you back 100 million
years in the Time Machine, okay?
But, before that...
I have to surprise Suneo.
Ahh...it's hot.
The bucket water warms up immediately.
Poor thing...
If not outside, how about we
play with water out back?
EH?!
Tha-that's still too risky!
Okay, now while we can P-suke.
Do you like it, P-suke?
This is the pool I used in Kindergarten.
Nobita
Aaaah, Mama!
O-0-0-000h, it's been a while
since I've used this pool.
It seems so long ago, that I was reminiscing
my kindergarten years.
Nobita,
Tell me the truth.
Lately, the fish and meats have been
disappearing in the refridgerator frequently...
You haven't picked up a stray
cat or dog, have you?
Wha-what? I swear to God, no.
If I find out that you have,
you'll be in big trouble...
You hear me?
Hai.
If I told her that I have a pet dinosaur,
Mama would probably faint from it.
So don't worry, I won't tell her.
He's gotten so big, we can't keep
secretly raise him anymore.
We should take him to the Cretacious
period already...
No, not yet. Not till he gets bigger so
I can make Suneo quack in his shoes.
Doraemon,
I let him loose in the pond at the park,
so we don't have to worry anymore.
Park?
He'll be okay.
I made sure he knows not to show
himself unless I call him.
Hmmm....I wonder if it'll work that simple.
PI
You know it's me by my footsteps?
Good boy.
Did you miss me?
I'm sorry I can only come here at night.
Tonight's treat is sausage.
See?
Here, eat up.
Here.
Sorry. Sorry.
P-suke, it started to rain, so I'll come back later.
P-suke!
P-suke...wonder how he's doing right now...
Oh, Doraemon. How was he?
Well, he won't eat at all.
Apparently, he misses you.
It's been three days since you
got sick and last saw him.
It's no surprise.
What's that sound?
Psuke!
You're not supposed to be here.
P-suke
What are we going to do if someone
saw you coming here?
Nobita-kun, he came to see you.
I see. P-suke.
Please understand.
I would love to visit you everyday too,
So, please be a good boy.
P-suke.
Doraemon,
Could you please take P-suke back to the park?
Okay.
C'mon. Let's go.
You gotta eat your food, okay?
I can't be lollygagging anymore.
Hey Suneo,
I'll show you the promised thing tonight.
Oh my, Nobita-chan. It's a holiday
starting today, right?
Suneo-chama has gone to Karuizawa
on an overnighter.
Shizuka-chan went on a one night trip too?
He went with his grandpa on a job
to the mountains to gather straw.
Giant too.
Then that means there's no one here.
Did you know?
There's a dinosaur in the lake at the park.
No way.
There are people who said they've seen it.
Oh?
The Wildlife Association claims it's impossible, but,
As the rumors spread, this station
cannot stand by idly.
And will be employing a submersible to verify...
And, we will update you, as soon as we can.
A A Monster in the Park's Lake.
D-d-d-doraemon, w-w-w-hat d-do
we do? What do we do?!
There is only one thing you can do.
Return P-suke back to his own
time, 100 million years past.
But..
Spaghetti...
Think about it, it is your dinosaur after all.
P-suke...
W-w-who are you?!
You're the one they call Nobita-kun, aren't you?
After observing you and your dinosaur,
we decided we want him for ourselves.
I-won't let you do as you p-please!
I'm leaving for now, but know that
I will return for your dinosaur.
There's no turning back
I have to return P-suke to his
time 100 milion years past.
Doraemon, Small Light
Yeah.
Here.
Doraemon, let's hurry.
Yeah.
That was not cool.
P-suke
Just a bit more.
What was that?
Wait!
As promised, I have come for that dinosaur.
It's the man in black from before.
You know him?
He's bad.
He's come to kidnap P-suke.
Okay.
Wait!
Tenacious kids.
Now hand over that dinosaur!
Uh-oh.
Doraemon, Big Light.
Yeah.
P-suke, this is your world.
Live a happy life here, you hear?
Take care then.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
A-a-ah. Hey. Hey.
No.
You're not supposed to follow us!
You hear?!
No!
P-suke! This is the best place for you to live!
Don't you understand?
Doraemon, let's go!
Yeah!
This time you didn't rely on me.
And thought things through,
Which is a significant improvement.
Hey! Nobita!
Nobita! You promised to eat
spaghetti through your nose.
Nobita-kun, it's Giant and Suneo.
What are you going to do?
You promised, now I wanna see you
eat that spaghetti with your nose.
B-but, I did raise a whole dinosaur, so.
I really did.
He's still saying it.
Have you no shame?
You gotta believe me, I'm telling you the truth.
Shut up!
Here! Eat it!
Mgh-ghugh
With your nose, eat it with your nose.
ACHOO!!
Wait!!
Shizuka-chan.
What are you doing up there?
...um...
I'm sorry. I'm being chased by Suneo and Giant.
The thing you promised?
Just let me hide here.
Well, it was a ridiculous deal you made there.
There are no living dinosaurs.
And you can't eat spaghetti with your nose.
If you go and apologize now, you guys will
be laughing about the whole thing later.
But...
But I did raise a dinosaur.
My.
Everyone lies when pressured sometime.
But being stubborn about it,
Is really unmanly.
If you insist, I'll show you.
I'll show you alright!
Hey, Doraemon.
Can we at least show P-suke on the Time TV.
It wouldn't be so bad if we just
watched him on TV, right?
Sure.
All right.
P-suke!
What's going on?
This is bad!
What?
P-suke is a Japanese Plesiosaur
And we sent him to the wrong place.
WHAT?
The Time Machine can go
to the past and future.
In other words, it travels through time.
But it also can move here and there,
Which means it also has a spatial function.
The man in black damaged the
spatial control mechanism,
Which caused this.
What wrong place do you think we sent him?
Looks like...
The North American Continent.
That is serious!
Doraemon, let's go get P-suke and take
him to Japan in the Cretacious period.
Hurry, Doraemon, hurry!
Ow-ow-ow-ow.
We'll go too. We can, can't we? Right?
You can't all fit. It'll be over the weight limit.
Doraemon
Aaaagh
What's the deal? Doraemon,
you botched the landing.
Where is Doraemon?
What will happen to us if
We can't find Doraemon?
Doraemon.
Over there
Goodness, gracious, Doraemon.
We left P-suke over there.
Yahoo!
P-suke!
P-suke.
It's P-suke!
Yahoo!
P-suke!
P-suke..P!
P-suke.
I missed you, P-suke.
I'm not worthy.
You win.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for not believing you.
It's okay.
But, see, I was telling the truth.
It's real. It's a real Futaba-Suzuki-Ryu.
Gah?
He's cute.
Over here.
He's tame.
Over here, over here.
I can't fix it.
Elasmosaurus platyurus.
Even though it's a Plesiosaur, the American
one differs from the Japanese.
So that's why they're unfriendly.
Don't worry, P-suke, we're here
to take you back to Japan.
Doraemon,
Let's hurry and take P-suke back to Japan.
Uh, about that...
Since we're here, 100 million years in the past,
How about we camp here overnight,
and go home tomorrow?
Woo hoo, woo hoo, it's camp
time, it's camp time.
But I haven't finished my homework,
And I'll get in trouble if I stay over anywhere
without asking my mom.
Yeah, yeah, Doraemon!
Don't say things irresponsibly!
Well...
It's not a problem.
We came in the Time Machine,
So it doesn't matter if we stay
here for a days or even years.
If we set it to five minutes after we left,
we'll only be gone for five minutes.
Let's play.
Let's swim with P-suke.
Agreed!
One moment.
You can make swimsuits with
this Kisekae Camera
You can draw your favorite
designs in this notebook.
Leave the designing to me.
This should do it.
Here.
Everyone line up, line up.
Eeek
Oops, sorry.
And then,
With this Air-tube you can breath underwater,
And with this Shinkai Cream you can withstand
any water temperature and water pressure.
Wow.
Yippee!
You're so cute.
Beautiful.
What's this, what's this?
Ah, an Ammonite
That's interesting
Doraemon, your pocket even has food.
I want to eat something better.
It's a luxury in this age.
If the dinosaurs find us, we're the meal.
Right?
What's the matter, Dora-chan?
O-oh, it's nothing.
You're a funny one, Doraemon.
Anyway,
When you say 100 million years ago,
How long ago, would 100 million years be?
Well, it's one year 100 million times.
But that doesn't really put it into perspective.
Isn't there a better way to describe it?
That's impossible.
For example,
When we hear stories about our grandparents,
Even though it seems long ago,
In reality, it would be at most 60 years, right?
Umm...
If you divide 100 million by 60
That means grandpa's, grandpa's grandpa...
I can't figure it out.
I thought so.
Anyhow, let's just say we came
pretty far back in time.
History is mystifying.
Since we finished dinner,
I would like to take this moment
to give you my recital.
Giant, you're gonna sing?
You got a problem with that, Nobita?
N-no, please sing
Really?
Dora-dora give it to them don-don-don.
I am a lively King.
Just like fireworks, don-don-don
I'm a prankster.
From up close I go don.
When school is over, I'm already there.
And to tomorrow, it's just as fun as today.
I'm Giant, full of energy.
And when tomorrow comes,
I'll have just as much fun.
I am Giant, the energetic...
St-stop, stop Giant!
The dinosaurs are gonna react to your singing!
What did you say?!
That won't happen!
Da d-da-da give it to them don-don-don!
I am Giant, full of energy!
G-Giant!
D-Doraemon, help us.
Doraemon, what are you doing?
I've had enough!
Let's go home already!
Yeah.
Let's take P-suke to the twentieth
century with us.
EHH?!
We can't go home?!
What do you mean?!
To be frank,
The traveling space device on the
Time Machine has been broken.
It can't be fixed.
In other words, we can't go home?
Well...we can still travel time.
So for an example, if we carry this Time
Machine to where Japan would be,
No, the Japan Islands weren't formed
yet back a 100 million years ago.
Where it would be in the future,
And to be exact, Tokyo's...
Nobita-kun's residence,
In Nobita-kun's room...
Nobita-kun's desk...
If we could put this Time Machine
on the exact position...
It's possible we can get back home.
But there's no way that that's possible.
Oknow. Doraemon,
Let's fly by the Take-copters.
No!
Take-copters fastest speed is 80 km,
If we use it continuously for eight
hours, the battery will die.
We can only go 640 km.
How much more distance do
you think it is to Japan?
Oh no...
Hey, hey, you piece of trash robot!
How dare you bring us to such
a place with a broken machine!
What the Hell are you talking about, Giant!
You were the one who jumped
in without asking.
That's why...that's why this happened
because of the overload.
What was that?!
Hey,
Everyone, listen up.
When we were playing with
the radio controller,
The battery died when it was
continuously played with,
But when we let it rest here and there,
It lasts a long time, remember?
Maybe we can apply that to the Take-copters?
Yeah.
Doraemon, it can, can't it?
It'll last longer, right?
YAY! We can go back home to Japan!!
Wait.
Where are we going to let it rest?
Between America and Japan, there's
the huge Pacific Ocean you know.
Hey, Suneo! How dare you talk nonsense to us.
No!
He's talking good sense.
Hey, hey, within the 100 million years,
the Earth has changed drastically.
So in this era, the Asian Continent
and America were connected.
see...
Then...
We can get home then?
To Japan?
Yup!
YAY~!
We can go home!
We can go home to Japan!
Hey, P-suke!
Come on, jump in.
Ok, let's take off!
It's just a little ways more.
I'll take you out as soon as I can, okay P-suke?
Let's stop here today, and make
a camp at that beach there.
Doraemon,
Take out the Big Light.
Here.
There.
We're going to camp here till morning.
Don't go far, okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
What? No, I'm busy.
Go on, go play!
Um...
Camping Capsule!
Where shall l...
Ummmm...
Okay everyone, jump on.
Our long journal has finally started.
Yahooo~!
This is great.
Dear Mother...
Hey, over here!
I can't walk anymore.
Take out the Take-copter.
Please?
No!
Is it okay if you don't return to Japan?
You need to walk!
Perfect!
Momotaro Brand, Kibidango.
Come on, let us ride you.
Wow. It's a real Brontosaurus.
It's not a fossil or a stuffed animal,
It's a real breathing Brontosaurus.
AHHHH, this is great!
What are you talking about? What if it eats you?
It's fine.
The Brontosaurus are herbivores
and calm. They're also slow.
As long as you be careful not to be stepped
on, you can get close to them.
Let's go Suneo. Hurry up and follow.
Watch out! Watch out!
Yay, it's a slide.
Wah, so cute.
Hey everyone, take a look at this.
What is it?
See?
It's such a cute newly born.
www
Oh no, the baby!
Ah, Shizuka-chan.
Ah, hey...
You need to run with us!
We got caught!
Do--Doraemon...
Oh, no. Not this...
It's not this, or that!
OH, not this either!
Momotaro Brand Kibidango!
There!
That was close.
Tyrannosaurus is our follower now.
You can play with it now.
Really?
Are you sure?
See?
Hey!
Yay!
I'm gonna make this my first findings.
Hey, Doraemon!
Shizuka-chan!
Shall we?
Take off!
Dear Mother...
Even though we were faced
with different incidents,
The crossing of the American
Continent is going well.
Mommy, forgive me!
Do-Doraemon!
The Take-copter is broken!
As soon as we find a good spot, let's land early.
Nobita, stop being a slowpoke.
When you're slow, it makes
a burden for the rest of us.
Nobita's slowness has infected his Take-copter.
You shouldn't say such a thing
when he's in trouble!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Shizuka-chan...
You can do it. We're almost there.
Yeah.
It's a Pterodactyl!
Hey, wait for me!
Kibidango! Kibidango! Kibidango!
Found it!
Oh darn...
Who are you guys?
Why are you guys following us?
You know, don't you? We
want your P-suke-kun.
Huh?
You can't!
I've been killing numerous dinosaurs
mainly of this era,
Or even catching them.
I've never seen such a human
friendly dinosaur as P-suke.
really want to have him.
I see!
What's a dinosaur hunter?
There's this time traveling law
called the Posted Law,
You're forbidden to capture creatures
from the pass without permission.
Because it'll change the history.
For example, the ancestors of humans are living
somewhere in this era as mammals and reptiles.
What will happen if they are killed?
It'll mean that humans were
never born on this Earth.
It'll mean that none of you would exist.
It's nothing that serious.
There are tons of dinosaurs.
It doesn't make a difference if we catch a few.
But you're breaking the law!
And for a profit!
There are rich people,
Who want stuffed Pterodactyl or the neck
of a Tyrannosaurus to put on their wall!
How could they?!
Like we could hand over P-suke
to such bad people!
Come on, you shouldn't jump to conclusions.
I'm not saying we want him for free.
On top of giving you tons of money,
We're willing to take you back to your era.
You're gonna take us back home?
Yes.
Talk it over amongst yourselves tonight,
Then come to our base.
We made it underground, just on the other side of
that waterfall, so the Time Patrol can't find us.
Like Hell we're going!!
So...you don't want to?
Then, we'll see you in the morning.
Hope to hear a good decision.
I'm a gentle-hearted man,
See ya
I can't take this no more!
I want to go back to Japan!
I had enough of adventuring!
But...
That's not good for P-suke-chan.
But, it's not like he's going to be eaten up, right?
He'll be sold to a rich person from the future,
And kept in their pool or something, right?
Do you think that's happiness for P-suke?
We have worked so hard
so that wouldn't happen.
Then, if we turn down his offer,
How do you intend on us getting back to Japan?
That's...
P-suke...
We can't just not care for P-suke-chan.
Suneo-kun, you feel the same, right?
Ye-yeah, if you all agree...
Yah, so it's you?
Did you get it? That human-friendly dinosaur?
It's as good as ours.
I was thinking that maybe you should
be the one to capture it on your own.
Since there's no way that the boy who
owns him will give him up easily.
We're probably going to be faced with
a bit of a commotion tomorrow.
Mister, you haven't yet experienced
human hunting, have you?
Okay, let's do it.
Number seven base? It's midway
of Northern America, is it?
Well then, we shall we waiting for you.
A buggie car...where did they hide it?
This is the last warning,
Hand over the dinosaur quietly!
This is...
This is a mud puppet too.
Damn.
Diverting us to such a thing...
Where did the real ones go?
Follow the radio waves.
If they're using a radio controller,
then they have to be somewhere!
Yes!
We've been tricked...
They said their base was hidden
behind the waterfall, right?
Yeah.
They probably would never think that we'd sneak into their
base and use their Time Machine to get back, would they?
But, I don't think we can hold them off
with those clay puppets for long.
The radio controller isn't working anymore.
EH?
Darn!
They've found us!
UC'FC GOING TO TAKE OVER THE TING
NACHING AND FCTURN TO JAPAN.
Take over the Time Machine?!
Unforgiveable!
I was nice thinking that they were kids,
But this is as far as I hold back.
No, no. We have their bait.
We know for sure that the remaining
two are headed here.
Shall we prepare to greet them?
Hurry!
Understood!
P-suke.
Doraemon!
Nobita-kun.
Ah, Doraemon!
P-suke.
I'm glad we found you.
No-Nobita-kun...
That, that!
P-suke,
You need to hold on.
Doraemon, let's go!
We need to hurry and find the others.
Yup!
Come on.
They're approaching the third entrance.
Shall we capture them?
Don't interfere with anything.
Mister,
Let us show you a grand show.
This door doesn't open at all.
The Slip-Through-Hoop.
Let us goooo!!!
Okay
Lure them to the competition room.
Help us!!
This way!
Mister, shall we get going?
Yeah.
Oh, have found an abnormal engine
wave in the Cretaceous Period.
It seems it's human made.
Okay.
Send in a scout.
I'm certain it's those unofficial hunters.
Time Patrol, number One. Deploy.
Help us!
Help us!!
That's Giant's voice.
Help us !!
Doraemo~n!
Suneo's voice too.
This way!
Yeah.
Shizuka-chan!
Help us, Doraemo~n!
What?!
Welcome.
Welcome to my sports arena.
I built this so that we can watch
dinosaurs fight each other.
Listen, can't you hear the blood-thirsty
dinosaurs all worked up?
The dinosaur will attack
you within five minutes.
If you want me to stop it, hand
over P-suke immediately.
Your time limit is five minutes.
Think it over.
We can't.
I don't care about that long-necked
dinosaur anymore.
This is more interesting. Let's
watch things from here,
Hirari Manteau.
I see...
You're the one that ate the
Kibidango the other day.
Wha-what? That useless fool!
The piece of crap dinosaur!
Yoshi! Let's beat them!
There he is...
A
They're coming!
Run!
Hirari Manteau.
Hirari~.
Hirari.
Wha-what?!
We're the time patrolers. Give yourselves up!
This is the end of your hunting game.
We shall escort you to the twenty-third
century's prison.
Give it up.
Isn't this good, P-suke?
The time...
For P-suke and I to depart has come.
This is your home.
Take care.
P-suke,
Why do you think that we tried
so hard to get you here?
Just listen to me already.
If not, I'm going to hit you.
P-suke!
P-suke! P-suke...
Saito-san...
Let's go while we can.
You sure? Well that's too bad.
Yay, we get to go home.
P-suke, take care.
Our target, Twentieth century,
Tokyo, Nobi residence.
Take off!
Good bye P-suke.
Promise you'll be happy~!
Good bye-!
Ojamashimasu.
What were you all doing upstairs?
Nothing much.
Well then Nobita-kun. See you later.
Yeah.
See ya!
Suneo, show me your homework, okay?
Sure.
We experienced life and
death together after all.
Good night.
P-suke...
J'm here
Inside your pocket
Together with you
To accompany you on your travels
J've been waiting
Till you realized
The dream you have dreamt
What could it be?
Let's go there right now together
Jt's a world that's distant yet close
Even in my pocket
There's an expansive sky
The clouds drift by
There's a wonderful world like this
A world that we travel
Even in my pocket
There's a vast ocean
Birds take flight
There's a wonderful world like this
A world that we travel